ANDHINI PUTRI ARINI

Surabaya 60298, Indonesia | +6282122803089 | andhiniputr@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/andhini-putri-arini-773835272

SUMMARY

I am a third year informatics student who oriented on issues as a new challenge, also have a grit that continuously develops, and ready for a new challenge. Looking further at every challenge as an opportunity to explore myself, I also always stick to honesty as the foundation of everything. Because I believe that honesty and trust are very valuable. Have experience in website development, machine learning, and interest in data science. I have good skills and experience in making projects individually also in groups.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF PEMBANGUNAN NASIONAL VETERAN EAST JAVA

(July 2021 - Present)

Bachelor of Informatics Computer Science Faculty

• GPA:3.9/4.00

UNIVERSITY OF PUTRA INDONESIA YPTK PADANG

(October 2020 - June 2021)

Bachelor of Informatics Computer Science Faculty

• GPA: 3.6/4.00

SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL 75, NORTH JAKARTA

(July 2017 – June 2020)

Graduated in Natural Sciences.

PROJECTS

REHES (RENTAL HEALTH STUFF)

(February - June 2023)

UI/UX Designer

- ReHes is a mobile-based application for rental of health stuff, this application will work with hospitals or clinics to facilitate rental. This application has just been realized in the form of a prototype.
- I worked on this project individually to create an application interface starting from the splash page to completion along with the prototype.
- Tools: Figma

BEKASTORE

(February – June 2023)

Back-end Developer

- BekaStore is a website e-commerce that can be used to sell preloved stuff, give away items for free as grant, and room rental.
- I worked as a group in this project, I happened to get a part in the back-end but also helped the front-end in some things such as working on certain pages.
- Tools: MySQL, PHP, JavaScript, Bootstrap

NOTIFY (May – June 2023)

Front-end Developer

- Notify is a website-based application for record tasks or create to do lists and reminders.
- I worked as a group in this project and got the responsibility to work on the front-end for this time I just focused on my part and completed the page according to the plan.
- Tools: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap

LIBRARY (May – June 2023)

Front-end Developer

- Library is a desktop-based application that can be used for recorded borrowed and returned books at the library and can display them in the form of history and record members.
- I worked in a group in this project and got the responsibility to work on the front-end for this time I just focused on my part and completed the page according to the plan.
- Tools: Java, MySQL

SOILINK (Nov 2023 – Present)

Machine Learning

- Soilink is an android-based application that functions to detect soil types and provide related information. The application will process the images received from the camera or manually uploaded from the gallery.
- I worked as a group on this project as a graduation requirement in Bangkit Academy and got the responsibility to build models for applications with the main goals of high accuracy and not overfitting.
- Tools: Python

EXPERIENCES

MACHINE LEARNING STUDENT

(Aug 2023 - Present)

Bangkit Academy led by Google, Tokopedia, Gojek, & Traveloka

- Learn about data analytics, mathematics for machine learning and data science, machine learning specialization, deeplearning, and model deployment with tensorflow
- Bangkit also provide us with soft skill and English class because using English is mandatory in Bangkit

IT INTERN BBWS BRANTAS

(Aug 2023 – Nov 2023)

Kementerian Pekerjaan Umum dan Perumahan Rakyat (PUPR)

• Regenerate website for employee recruitment and responsible as front-end in this individual project

HEAD OF COMMUNITY SERVICE

(May 2023 - Present)

- BEM FASILKOM UPN "Veteran" Jawa Timur
- Supervises four members and responsible for them also planning all events and divide responsibilities to each member
- Monitor all of the events (3 big events and 2 agendas) and evaluating the performance of each member and the event that is their responsibility

STAFF OF COMMUNITY SERVICE

(May 2022 – May 2023)

BEM FASILKOM UPN "Veteran" Jawa Timur

 Be responsible for community social issues and become a stimulus for BEM FASILKOM to foster a sense of caring, responsive, solutive, and active

STAFF OF SECURITY DIVISION OF MOSAIK

(August 2022)

BEM FASILKOM UPN "Veteran" Jawa Timur

- Organize and prepare for the arrangement of all activities related to event security such as student mobilization, parking areas, rallying points, and coordinate at all times with other divisions in case of any emergencies.
- Successfully secured the event and ensured that there were no violations or disturbances during the event, which was attended by 600 students

CHIEF EXECUTIVE OF DONOR DARAH

(September 2022)

BEM FASILKOM UPN "Veteran" Jawa Timur

- Leading all committee members so that each division runs according to a predetermined plan and coordinate with each division
- Successfully achieved the target by bringing in more than 70 participants and managed to get 33 blood bags

DEPUTY CHIEF EXECUTIVE OF FUN DAY WITH FASILKOM

(September 2022)

BEM FASILKOM UPN "Veteran" Jawa Timur

- Responsible for the continuity of the event with the chief executive and assist the chief executive in coordinating all
 committees and events
- Successfully taught and educated 37 abandoned children and street children.

HEAD OF EVENTS DIVISION OF ABDI DESA

(October 2022)

BEM FASILKOM UPN "Veteran" Jawa Timur

- Determine the theme and concept of the event also set the PIC of each event
- Successfully ran the event according to the predetermined rundown such as teaching 4th, 5th, and 6th grade, helping digitize the sellers, cleaning the village environment, and socializing with the villagers.

TREASURER OF OPEN TALK

(November 2022)

BEM FASILKOM UPN "Veteran" Jawa Timur

Make a draft budget, record all financial matters, and record evidence of expenses

HEAD OF EVENTS OF HIMATIFA DESIGN CONTEST

(November 2022)

HIMATIFA UPN "Veteran" Jawa Timur

- Determine the theme and concept of the event also make rundown for event, technical meeting, and mentoring
- Successfully ran the event according to the predetermined rundown such as conducting seminars about design that attended by expert speakers and more than 50 participants, running a design competition with a total of 5 participants, and mentoring participants with experts before submitting the final results.

CERTIFICATIONS

Mathematics for Machine Learning and Data Science Specialization

(September 2023)

(October 2023)

DeepLearning.Al

Credential ID: AYHGX666SRFB

URL: https://coursera.org/share/24ca353d4d0746f33f7264fd3f3bf609

Machine Learning Specialization

DeepLearning.Al

Credential ID: JKMN46KN9SHX

URL: https://coursera.org/share/5ba587c0a5334495951d956b5b60f7d3

DeepLearning.AI TensorFlow Developer Specialization (November 2023)

DeepLearning.Al

Credential ID: 2XXLCC2KC9BS

URL: https://coursera.org/share/b66995afd193c98cf79e732da71715b7

Structuring Machine Learning Projects (November 2023)

DeepLearning.Al

Credential ID: Y4QDZZKCMCBE

URL: https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/Y4QDZZKCMCBE

TensorFlow: Data and Deployment Specialization (November 2023)

DeepLearning.Al

Credential ID: U3NJ34EBKG5L

URL: https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/specialization/certificate/U3NJ34EBKG5L

SKILLS AND INTERESTS

Skills : SQL, Python, C, Java, HTML, CSS, PHP, CI

Tools : Dev-C, Visual Studio Code, NetBeans, Figma, MySQL WorkBench, Bootstrap

Interests : Web Development, Machine Learning, Data Analytics

LANGUAGES

English : Limited working proficiency
Indonesian : Native or bilingual proficiency
Japanese : Elementary proficiency